lsbu.ac.uk 2017-12-14

# Privacy | London South Bank University

London South Bank University (LSBU) is committed to protecting your privacy

## Data protection

We do not collect personal information from visitors to our website unless you explicitly and intentionally provide it. Personal information is collected in compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Personal information will be held securely and not passed on to others, unless you have given your consent or requested by law.

[More about data protection at LSBU](http://www.lsbu.ac.uk/footer/foi/data-protection "Data protection at LSBU"). 

All our web pages are designed to comply with the [JANET Acceptable Use Policy](https://community.ja.net/library/acceptable-use-policy "JANET Acceptable Use Policy"). 

## Visitor statistics

We collect and analyse statistics relevant to website usage. This information is used to help us improve the usability and performance of our website. Visitor statistics do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users. Data is used in aggregate and analysed collectively, rather than on an individual basis. We sometimes read IP address information so that we can distinguish between internal and external traffic and deliver a customised experience for our respective audiences. However, we do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics and Google Adwords Conversion tracker which both set cookies on a browser. Data collected by these cookies, which are set and read by Google, provide us with valuable insights which help us increase the effectiveness of our website for visitors. 

We also use data collected by the Google DoubleClick cookie which provides us with Google Analytics Demographics, Interest Reporting and 3rd party audience data, such as age ranges and interests, to further help us understand how people find and use our site and help us to provide a better user experience. We may use this information to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with London South Bank University.

We will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the Google DoubleClick cookie unless we have robust notice of, and the user's prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger.

Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en "Google ad settings opt out information").  

Alternatively, visitors can also use the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Advertising and remarketing

As you browse the London South Bank University website, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners, [AdRoll](http://www.adroll.com/), [DoubleClick](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/ "DoubleClick") and [Google](https://www.google.co.uk/ "Goolge")  then enable us to present you with remargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with London South Bank University. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. 

Visitors can opt-out of [AdRoll](http://www.adroll.com/), [DoubleClick](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/ "DoubleClick") and [Google](https://www.google.co.uk/ "Goolge")  targeted advertising and that of other third parties by visiting the [Networks Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

## Further information

For more detailed information on what cookies are and which ones are set across the LSBU website and what they are used for, please visit our [dedicated cookie usage page](http://www.lsbu.ac.uk/footer/cookies "Cookie usage page").

Top of page
